You like this film, buy it !
Come on, sweetie pie.
Morning, Elvis.
You're a pretty Elvis, aren't you?.
Yes, you are.
Jesus Christ, Ronnie, you know
I have to fucking work tonight.
Somebody around here
has got to make some money.
I'm all broken up here, bitch.
I can't work.
- Yeah, and whose fault is that?.
- Fuck you.
Oh, my God, you're pathetic.
You know that new waitress
over at the Bingo Lounge?.
She's been giving me the freaky eye.
Oh, the whore with the big tits
hanging down to her knees?.
Maybe I'll choke the chicken,
purge my snorkel
all over them flappy-ass tits.
Good. Well, have
a good fucking time.
- I will.
- I hope she likes cripples.
Bitch, I will crawl over there,
and I will skull fuck the shit outta you!
Oh, I'll get the crutches for you.
See what you did?.
Fucking loudmouth.
Waah! Waah!
That's all that fucker does is cry.
Cry and shit. Cry and shit.
Just like you.
That's all you do is cry and shit.
Fuck you and set it
on my pole right now, bitch.
Fuck off.
Mom?.
Can't you see I'm making eggs over here?.
I'll pass.
Since when?.
Since now. They're chicken abortions,
and they're fucking gross.
They are not chicken abortions.
Like you know what an abortion is.
You know what, can you please
go upstairs and get your brother?.
Why do I always have to do it?.
Just do it!
Don't you give me that look!
Man, that bitch got herself
a nice little dumper.
- What did you just say?.
- You heard me.
No, say it again, Ronnie!
Say it to my face!
Oh, what's the matter?.
You jealous of your own daughter's ass?.
- Fucking pig.
- Aah!
You fucking whore!
All right, now clean it up!
- Go on.
- I'm not gonna do this anymore!
Michael.
Stop jerking off in there.
Get away!
Hey! Get your ass downstairs
and wash your hands, you little shit.
I'm not listening!
Aaaahhh!
Let me tell you something.
That freak of yours,
he needs some serious discipline.
I mean, he runs around like a little bitch.
You leave him alone.
Keep your hands off him.
Give me a fucking break.
He's probably a queer.
He's gonna grow up,
end up cutting his dick and balls off
and changing his name to Michelle.
There he is.
Good morning, Michelle, ma belle.
What the hell took you two so long?.
Elvis died. I had to flush him.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
We'll get you a new one
after school, okay?.
Okay.
What'd you do to him,
stroke him to death?.
Uh, Elvis.
Elvis! Uh! Uh! Uh!
You know what?.
It's a fucking rat.
Who pays money for a fucking rat?.
I mean, it's a goddamn rat, man.
Morning, Boo.
"Morning, Boo."
Take that damn thing off.
You are starting to annoy me, boy.
I hate you.
And I hate you, too. You see this?.
As soon as this heals,
I'm gonna break it again on your fucking face!
Enough, all right?.
Can we just eat in peace for once?.
What a fucking pussy, dude.
I told you he wouldn't fight.
He's all fucking talk.
I was like-- We were fighting, right?.
You were there. He was like,
"I'm not gonna fight you." I was like--
Yes!
I know where he lives.
- You want to egg his house?.
- We can totally do that.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
Hey, shit-pants.
What's going on?. You know, um...
I heard your sister got caught
selling blow jobs in the bathroom.
I heard they had to pump the cum
out of her stomach.
Hey, Mikey, how's your mom doing?.
You know, my old man said that for a buck
she'd rub her tits on his face.
Shut up.
What the fuck did you say, faggot?.
- Mikey's upset.
- Look how tough he is.
Hey, ball-licker, check this out.
I was thinking of making copies of Mommy
for the whole school.
- Fuck you.
- Hey! Tough guy!
Think she'd suck my dick for a quarter
and let me suck her tits?.
- Shut up! Shut up!
- Don't fucking yell in my face, you bitch!
Fuck off!
What the hell is going on here?.
Break it up!
I said break it up!
You over there,
you over there, you there.
- He started it.
- Shut up!
Fuck you.
What did you say, son?.
I said fuck you.
Fuck me?.
Come here.
- My bag!
- Grab it!
Again?. Again?. Jesus, what is it with you
and this goddamn school?.
I cannot keep coming down here like this.
Look, Miss Myers,
I do not enjoy calling you down here
every five minutes.
Really?.
It sure seems like you fucking do.
Can't you get control
over your school, principal?.
Yes, I can get control.
I can control my school.
There's something you gotta know.
Will you just relax a moment?.
Please sit down and let me talk to you.
- Please. Please.
- Okay. What?.
Please, sit down.
- Thank God.
- Hi, Jim. How are you?.
Is this her?.
Miss Myers, this is Dr. Loomis.
I took the liberty of calling him in.
- Happens to be a child psychologist--
- Thank you, Jim.
Psychologist?.
May I ask you,
has your son ever had any kind
of serious psychiatric evaluation?.
Okay, I've had enough.
This is crazy.
- Miss Myers, please.
- I gotta get back to work.
- I gotta go.
- Please, ma'am.
We only want the best for the child.
Please don't take offense.
Please, sit down. Sit down.
Thank you.
Look, uh, Miss Myers...
we found this...
in Michael's school bag.
Come on. Big deal.
He found a dead cat.
And these.
What is that?.
I hope you're not squeamish, Mrs. Myers.
Oh, God.
Oh, this is really sick.
Are you saying Michael did this?.
Michael loves animals. He--
Why would he do this?.
Mrs. Myers, typically the thrill of hurting
or causing pain to smaller creatures,
it's often an early warning sign.
Early warning sign for what?.
For much deeper and bigger problems.
What do you mean problems?.
What is this?.
He's a very disturbed young man.
I have to evaluate him,
and I'd like to interview him.
I need to take him
through a series of tests.
Well, you can talk to him,
but what does--
what does evaluating him
what does that mean ?
Obviously, he's a very deranged
young mind that can do this to his pets.
You don't know that he did that.
Fuck, man, if I get one more fucking detention,
I'll be fucking expelled.
My old man's gonna beat my ass.
We gotta get that piece of shit
on the weekend so we don't get in trouble.
Dude, if I see that Myers pussy,
he's fucking dead.
You want it?.
Huh?. Do you want it?.
Aah!
Ow!
What the fuck?.
Oh, you're so fucking dead.
Oh, please stop.
Stop!
Please.
Please no!
I'm sorry.
Don't hurt me. Just-- I'm sorry.
No, no, no, don't.
Don't. Please. Please.
Please.
Don't hurt me.
No.
Hey, clown.
Hey.
Psycho boy.
Cat killer.
Do you really torture and kill
all them worthless animals, boy?.
Make you feel like a real bad-ass
motherfucker killer, huh?.
That is some deep-ass,
serious, faggoty-ass shit, man.
Judith, I'm gonna be late!
"Judith, I'm gonna be late!"
You really are a whiny little bitch,
you know that?.
Ronnie, knock it off.
Ma, Judith is wasting all my time.
I really shouldn't even let you go
after that shit you pulled today at school.
Oh, Ma, please?.
All right, Michael, calm down.
Tomorrow things are gonna change
around here,
so I suggest you live it up tonight.
Judith!
Here.
What?.
Would you do me a favor and please
take your brother trick-or-treating?.
Why don't you have that subhuman sloth
over there on the couch do it?.
You know, if I could get that lazy drunk
off his fat ass, I would.
Bitch, if you don't think I ain't making
a mental list of all your fucking bullshit!
Sweetie, look at me.
I know things have been bad,
but tomorrow we start to make
everything better, okay?.
- Yeah.
I like your hair curly.
It looks pretty.
Thanks, sweetie.
Have fun trick-or-treating, okay?.
Don't eat too much candy.
Hey, Mrs. Myers.
I want you out by 1 1.
- What'd I do?.
- I know what you do.
Whatever.
What about trick-or-treating?.
Are you kidding me?.
Go by yourself.
Aren't you too old for that, anyway?.
Whatever.
Sorry, squirt, but have fun.
Trick or treat!
## [Love Hurts]
# Love hurts #
# Love scars #
# Love wounds #
# And marks #
# Any heart #
# Not tough #
# Or strong #
# Enough #
# To take a lot of pain #
# Take a lot of pain #
# Love is like a cloud #
# Holds a lot of rain #
# Love hurts #
# Ooh, ooh, love hurts #
What if your dad hears us?.
Hold up, man.
That fucking drunk-prick fuck Ronnie
ain't my dad.
Okay, l-- I didn't know.
My daddy's in heaven, okay?.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Close your eyes.
Keep them closed, all right?.
I got a surprise for you.
Open.
Aaarrrgghhh!
Aaahh!
- Wow.
- What?.
Take that stupid thing off.
Oh, come on, babe.
I want to do it with the mask on.
Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh! Uhh! Uhh!
[(Don't Fear) The Reaper
playing in headphones]
Steve, stop it.
Stop.
Once a night is enough.
Stop it.
Michael?.
Michael, what the fuck
are you doing in here?.
Answer me.
Michael.
Michael!
Answer me!
What the fuck--
Michael!
Answer
Happy Halloween, Boo.
Jesus, what the hell happened now?.
Sweetie, what are you doing out here?.
It's freezing.
Michael, what's going on?.
Michael, answer me.
Give me the baby.
Michael, what is going on?.
Answer me.
... in connection
with tonight's brutal murders.
...the Myers family,
and was described by police
as Manson-like in its viciousness,
and more horrific than anything
Hollywood could imagine.
Judith Myers' nude body
was found lying face-down
in a pool of blood in an upstairs hallway.
Apparently she had been stabbed 17 times.
Her boyfriend Steven Haley's body
was found in the kitchen downstairs,
the victim of an apparent vicious beating
with an aluminum baseball bat.
Along with Myers and Haley,
a third victim, Ronnie White,
who was found bound to a chair,
White's neck slit wide open
with a kitchen knife
and stabbed numerous times
in the face and chest.
Of course we'll have much more
on this horrific story as it develops.
But for now,
three people brutally murdered,
and a 1 0-year-old boy, Michael Myers,
being held in custody.
I'm standing outside
Smith's Grove Sanitarium
where late last night,
1 0-year-old Michael Myers was transferred
after being found guilty
of first-degree murder.
Myers' verdict comes
after one of the lengthiest
and most expensive trials
in the state's history.
In attendance during this trial,
Dr. Samuel Loomis.
Loomis has now been appointed
by Judge Masterson
to oversee Myers' care
while incarcerated here at Smith 's Grove.
Hello, hello, hello.
Can you talk in there?.
Hi, I'm Michael Myers.
Okay, okay. That's fine.
That's good. That's good.
Okay, we're on.
How are you feeling today?.
Good.
Could I ask you something?.
You can ask me
whatever you want.
That's why I'm here.
If you have anything on your mind,
feel free-- anything.
Okay.
Why do you talk so funny?.
Talk so funny?.
Tell me, Michael,
what do you remember about...
that night, Halloween?.
What do you mean,
like my costume and candy?.
So you remember nothing
about the killing?.
You remember nothing
about getting a knife?.
- I didn't do that.
- Oh, okay.
But you were covered in blood.
Whose blood was it?.
I don't know.
Case: Michael Myers.
To the untrained eye,
there's nothing visually abnormal
with this angelic young boy,
but one must remember not to be fooled
by his calm, unassuming facade.
Can I go home today?.
No, not today.
Tomorrow?.
I don't know.
I have to talk to the doctor about that.
- Hey, Mommy.
- Yeah.
Is everyone at home okay?.
Everything's okay at home.
Okay.
Hey, Mikey.
How you doing?.
Look, you can't let those walls
get you down.
Believe me, I know.
I spent a little time behind walls.
I know they can drive you crazy.
You gotta look beyond the walls.
You know,
learn to live inside your head.
Hey, there's no walls
that can stop you there.
All right, I gotta get back to work.
Now you take it easy, Mikey.
Look at my mask.
Oh, wow. Beautiful. Yeah.
Why is it all black?.
'Cause it's one of my favorite colors.
Well, actually black isn't a color, is it?.
It's the absence of color.
In the spectrum of colors,
you go from black,
which is no color,
all the way through to white,
which is every color.
So technically--
not that it really matters--
but black isn't a color.
Why did you make it?.
I have my secrets.
Wait a minute.
I thought we had no secrets,
you and l.
Because no one sees me.
Yes, they do.
I see you every day.
Your mom, she comes every week.
Anybody else?.
No.
Michael has begun to obsess
on the construction
of these primitive masks.
It is the rare occasion
that he will allow himself
to be seen without one of these.
Only during the weekly visits
from his mother
does he show brief glimpses of the boy
he once may have been.
Do you like my mask?.
When did you make this?.
Just yesterday.
I like the mask because it hides my face.
I don't like you to hide your face.
Take it off.
It hides my ugliness.
Sweetie, don't say that.
Take it off.
You're not ugly.
Don't talk like that, okay?.
Okay.
I miss you so much.
I miss you, too.
Michael's so-called normal moments
are becoming fewer and fewer,
and I'm particularly worried about this.
I believe that these masks have
begun to create a mental sanctuary
in which Michael can hide
within himself and from himself.
# Deck the halls with boughs of holly,
Fa la la la la, la la la la #
Fuck you! Fuck you all!
- I hate you!
- Let it out!
Shut the fuck up!
I gotta get out of here.
Just let me out!
I hate this world!
- I don't want to be here anymore.
- I know. It's okay.
- I just want to go home.
- It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Why can't I just go home?.
Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'm afraid you can't go home.
Why?.
Because you've done terrible things.
Come here. Come on.
It's okay. It's okay, Michael.
Michael's downward slide
into this hellish abyss continues.
I fear he's on the verge
of completely shutting down.
I managed to persuade the suits
to let you come outside
and sit out in the garden.
All right, gardens.
Hardly a charming place,
but at least there's a bit of greenery.
But please, I mean,
if you don't communicate with me,
how can I help you?.
I'm here to help you.
I feel an utter failure at the moment,
that I just can't get through to you.
And you know, they're going
to see in my reports
that you're not responding, and--
you know, they may
take me off the case.
I don't know. I hope not.
I need to get out of here.
Yes, that's not going to happen
for a while, Michael.
Michael, take off the mask.
Honey, you don't look good.
You have to eat. Come on.
- Put my mask back on.
- Michael.
Please put my mask back on.
Come on.
Let's try to enjoy the day.
The child christened Michael Myers
has become a sort of ghost,
a mere shape of a human being.
There's nothing left here now.
Well, before I go,
I brought you something.
I found it. I thought you might like
to hang it up in your room.
I thought you'd like it.
Well, I guess I'll see you next week.
I'll walk you to the car.
Bye, sweetie.
Nurse, sit with Michael.
I'm taking Mrs. Myers to her car.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
Cute baby.
Couldn't be related to you.
You know, he's been silent now
for two weeks almost.
We really may want to consider
maybe shock treatments.
What happened?.
What happened there?.
Hey!
So you don't fucking talk a lot,
do you, Max?.
Goddamn it, we're gonna get
one thing straight.
I don't work for you.
You may have worked here
for many years
and done all manner of things,
and I suppose that's because
you're a hard worker.
Most of you people are.
All your women keep
your little bungalows clean,
sweep off the dirt floors--
keep the papooses in order and all--
but I'm my own boss, all right?.
I retire in about three months,
and you're still gonna be here
for a long time.
Now open the door.
Don't take no orders from anybody.
Let's go, fuck-nut. Time to go.
- Hey! Don't touch those.
- What?.
He doesn't like it
when you touch the masks.
God damn, I wouldn't want
the bum to freak out.
Sorry about these chains, Mikey.
What do you mean,
you're sorry about these chains?.
You got feelings for this big idiot,
is that what it is?.
What's the dig goin' on, lsmael?.
What the fuck, man?.
You know what?. I've been taking care
of this kid for almost 20 years.
And me and him--
You know what?. Never mind.
Just shut up, man.
Just keep your hands off his things.
Don't look at me.
I'll be a shitstorm
in your worst nightmare, motherfucker.
I'll come in here and fuck this place up
one night, you watch.
I really don't know what else to say, Michael.
You haven't said a word for 15 years.
Christ, that's a lifetime.
That's nearly twice as long
as my first marriage.
Wow.
It's strange, Michael.
In a weird way, you've become like...
... Iike my best friend.
It just shows you how fucked up my life is.
I've done all I possibly can for you.
So I'm sorry to tell you
that this is going to be my last day.
Michael...
I have to move on.
I'm sorry.
Take care, Michael.
Take care.
These eyes will deceive you.
They will destroy you.
They will take from you your innocence...
your pride...
and eventually your soul.
These eyes do not see
what you and I see.
Behind these eyes
one finds only blackness,
the absence of light.
These are the eyes...
of a psychopath.
Michael was created
by a perfect alignment
of interior and exterior factors
gone violently wrong--
a perfect storm, if you will.
Thus creating a psychopath
that knows no boundaries...
and has no boundaries.
Kendall, I really don't appreciate
being called out of
my favorite watering hole
to come down on
the fuckin' graveyard shift.
If you do me dirt on this one,
I'll fuckin' hold it against you.
Hey, you know what?. I'll fuck her.
You don't want to fuck her?.
I'll fuck her. Right here.
Mikey, Mikey, Mikey.
Here we go.
I want you to meet Cousin Noel.
- Hi, there, sweetie. Hi.
- Huh?.
Oh, we're just here to look in on you.
We know it's your first night and all.
We just want to see how you are. Oh!
- Aren't you a pretty little thing?.
- Not bad, huh?.
We're just makin' sure everything's okay.
Oh, now, we're okay. Hey.
Ooh, look at those little titties.
You're right!
Oh, look at there.
- What else is under there?.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, yeah! Whoo!
We got ourselves a fighter!
A fresh one!
You done good, cousin.
Hah-hah!
- I got an idea.
- Okay.
I got me a fuckin' bona fide,
sure as shit idea!
- Keep her fuckin' quiet.
- God, shut up.
Oh, Mikey, Mikey, Mikey, Mikey, Mikey.
Hello, Mike!
Hey, Mikey. We brought you
a little company.
Yeah, we got you
some new, fresh meat, baby.
Fuckin' bitch.
You want some of that?.
- Come on, baby!
- Show us you're a man, huh?.
You want some fuckin' pussy?.
Yeah.
You want some fuckin' pussy, huh?.
Yeah. Mm, that's good.
How 'bout some of that, killer?.
He ain't gonna do it.
Let me lick--
Let me just--
- You wanna fuckin' fight, huh?.
- Come on, bitch.
- Fuck the shit outta her.
- Come on! Get on her!
- Yeah, baby!
You fucking tard-ass faggot, come on!
Yeah!
You a faggot, boy?.
You a faggot, huh?.
What the fuck?.
Hey, you son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch!
Let him go.
Kendall!
What the fuck, Mikey?.
It's Kendall.
It's Kendall, Mikey.
Gloria?.
En el nombre del Padre, y del Hijo,
y del Espiritu Santo...
Mikey, what are you doing
out of your room?.
Okay...
Now, don't do nothing
we're both gonna regret later,
okay, Mikey?.
I'm gonna have to get you back
into your room, okay now?.
Let me get these.
I'm just gonna...
get these handcuffs and...
I'm gonna try to put these handcuffs
on you right now, Mikey.
And then we'll get you back
into your own bed, okay?.
Mikey!
I was good to you, Mikey.
Hello.
- Sam.
- Who is this?
Sam, it's Koplenson.
Who?.
Dr. Koplenson from Smith's Grove.
He's out.
Michael's out.
Shit. What?.
He broke out a few hours ago.
Sam, it's a--
it's a fucking massacre.
I'm coming right away.
All right.
Oh, shit.
## ["Tom Sawyer"]
# A modern-day warrior
Mean, mean stride #
# Today's Tom Sawyer
Mean, mean pride #
Oh, fuck!
Gotta leave the truck.
All right, boys.
Grizzley's back in town.
Who's got the Cracker Jacks?.
Grizzley's back!
All right!
Look it here.
That's a new paint job.
Don't mess it up. Don't scratch it.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Oh, my goodness.
Ooh!
# The world is,
the world is love and... #
Naughty girl.
Naughty, naughty girl.
Hey, buddy,
just to give you a heads up,
I got a taco deluxe supreme
talking back at me,
so I'm going to be a while.
So do you mind waiting somewhere else
and let me pass this beast in peace?.
Look, brother...
if you're looking for some kind of action,
you better take it on the arches
before I'm done dropping this load.
Or you're going to be one sorry A-hole.
I see.
What we got here is...
a failure to communicate.
You just hold on, Daisy.
I've got something for you.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Joe Grizzley, bitch.
And I'm going to cut that mask
right off your face, you--
Get-- Get back!
I ain't scared!
Come on, what--
# Mr. Sandman... #
Mason, Laurie!
- Morning.
Where are my goddamn glasses?.
- Jesus, Cynth, I'm gonna be late.
- On your head.
- Oh, sh-- I'm gonna lose my mind.
- Move.
Excuse me.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Now what?.
It says here Nickel's Hardware
is going out of business.
42 years and that's it, over and done.
Yeah, well, good. They're a rip-off.
And Mr. Nickels is a horny old pervert.
Okay, don't even want to know.
Guess what, Mom.
Mr. Nickels likes to touch me
the wrong way.
Ooh, whoo, Mommy!
Okay, that is so not funny.
Want a screwdriver, Mommy?.
You want a hammer?.
Look at this, Mom. Oh!
- Laurie, stop!
- I'm sorry. Okay.
- Are you eating?.
- No, I'll get something at school.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, sure.
Just let the faceless marauding
corporate monsters of America
destroy everything
beautiful about this town.
Corporate monsters or not,
Epic Mart's a lot cheaper.
Oh, man, I gotta get out of here.
- Thanks again for dropping that thing off.
- No sweat, Dad.
Just shove the envelope
inside the mail slot, okay?.
Yeah, Dad, I know.
They're coming by to look at it later, honey.
- So, it's very important that--
- Dad, okay.
I understand.
Muy importante.
- Love you.
- Love you, too.
Have a good day.
Mason, you forgot your briefcase, honey.
- Ah, shit.
I feel like "What round is it?"
Yeah.
Oh, uh, you think you could...
glue Mr. Bones' arms on or something?.
- Have a good day, baby.
- Yeah. Top on my priority list.
Hey, Laurie!
- Wait up!
- Oh, God.
- Leave me alone, Tommy.
- Wait.
Definition: stop walking.
- Can I ask you something serious?.
- Sure, why not?.
Did you ever hear
about the Mexican Wolf Man?.
- No.
- Yeah, well, he's real.
- I saw him on TV last night...
- Yeah.
And his name's Danny, and his face
is completely covered with hair.
And he likes soccer.
I swear it! They showed--
- Okay.
- He's a wolf!
Tommy, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Lay off the candy corn, kid.
Stop acting like I'm crazy. It's true!
Tommy, I'm your babysitter.
You're crazy.
- I know this. You're crazy.
- Ooohhh!